https://www.nzflowers.co.nz/privacy-policy

2020 University of Auckland December Graduation
Protecting your privacy is important to Iain Stephens Floral Design.
We are invested in protecting your privacy. We will not sell, trade or rent the information you supply us to any third party, unless required to by law.
We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Iain Stephens Floral Design Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service.
Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.
Iain Stephens Floral Design collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, updates, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about.
How we collect personal information
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service.
Iain Stephens Floral Design safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures.
We urge you also to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.
When you browse Iain Stephens Floral Design website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse not even your e-mail address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.
To make sure your personal information remains confidential. If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via e-mail using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.
Protecting your privacy is important to Iain Stephens Floral Design. We strive to keep your personal information confidential.
By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Iain Stephens Floral Design Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service.
